trainings.push(
    {
        name: "CSS-Basis-Training",
        description: "",

        fragen: [
    {
        "antwort":  "color",
        "kategorie":  "Color Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the color of text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "opacity",
        "kategorie":  "Color Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the opacity level for an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "background",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "A shorthand property for setting all the background properties in one declaration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "background-attachment",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets whether a background image is fixed or scrolls with the rest of the page"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "background-color",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the background color of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "background-image",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies one or more background images for an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "background-position",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the position of a background image"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "background-repeat",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets how a background image will be repeated"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "background-clip",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the painting area of the background"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "background-origin",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies where the background image(s) is/are positioned"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "background-size",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the size of the background image(s)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets all the border properties in one declaration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-bottom",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets all the bottom border properties in one declaration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-bottom-color",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the color of the bottom border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-bottom-left-radius",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Defines the shape of the border of the bottom-left corner"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-bottom-right-radius",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Defines the shape of the border of the bottom-right corner"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-bottom-style",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the style of the bottom border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-bottom-width",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the width of the bottom border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-color",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the color of the four borders"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-image",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "A shorthand property for setting all the border-image-* properties"
    },
    {   
        "antwort":  "border-image-outset",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the amount by which the border image area extends beyond the border box"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-image-repeat",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies whether the border image should be repeated, rounded or stretched"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-image-slice",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies how to slice the border image"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-image-source",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the path to the image to be used as a border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-image-width",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the widths of the image-border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-left",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets all the left border properties in one declaration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-left-color",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the color of the left border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-left-style",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the style of the left border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-left-width",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the width of the left border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-radius",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "A shorthand property for setting all the four border-*-radius properties"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-right",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets all the right border properties in one declaration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-right-color",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the color of the right border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-right-style",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the style of the right border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-right-width",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the width of the right border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-style",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the style of the four borders"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-top",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets all the top border properties in one declaration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-top-color",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the color of the top border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-top-left-radius",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Defines the shape of the border of the top-left corner"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-top-right-radius",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Defines the shape of the border of the top-right corner"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-top-style",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the style of the top border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-top-width",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the width of the top border"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-width",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the width of the four borders"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "box-decoration-break",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the behaviour of the background and border of an element at page-break, or, for in-line elements, at line-break."
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "box-shadow",
        "kategorie":  "Background and Border Properties",
        "frage":  "Attaches one or more drop-shadows to the box"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "bottom",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the bottom position of a positioned element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "clear",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies which sides of an element where other floating elements are not allowed"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "clip",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Clips an absolutely positioned element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "display",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies how a certain HTML element should be displayed"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "float",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies whether or not a box should float"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "height",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the height of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "left",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the left position of a positioned element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "margin",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets all the margin properties in one declaration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "margin-bottom",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the bottom margin of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "margin-left",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the left margin of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "margin-right",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the right margin of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "margin-top",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the top margin of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "max-height",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the maximum height of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "max-width",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the maximum width of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "min-height",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the minimum height of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "min-width",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the minimum width of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "overflow",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies what happens if content overflows an element\u0027s box"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "overflow-x",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies whether or not to clip the left/right edges of the content, if it overflows the element\u0027s content area"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "overflow-y",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies whether or not to clip the top/bottom edges of the content, if it overflows the element\u0027s content area"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "padding",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets all the padding properties in one declaration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "padding-bottom",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the bottom padding of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "padding-left",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the left padding of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "padding-right",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the right padding of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "padding-top",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the top padding of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "position",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the type of positioning method used for an element (static, relative, absolute or fixed)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "right",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the right position of a positioned element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "top",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the top position of a positioned element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "visibility",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies whether or not an element is visible"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "width",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the width of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "vertical-align",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the vertical alignment of an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "z-index",
        "kategorie":  "Basic Box Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the stack order of a positioned element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "align-content",
        "kategorie":  "Flexible Box Layout",
        "frage":  "Specifies the alignment between the lines inside a flexible container when the items do not use all available space"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "align-items",
        "kategorie":  "Flexible Box Layout",
        "frage":  "Specifies the alignment for items inside a flexible container"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "align-self",
        "kategorie":  "Flexible Box Layout",
        "frage":  "Specifies the alignment for selected items inside a flexible container"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "flex",
        "kategorie":  "Flexible Box Layout",
        "frage":  "Specifies the length of the item, relative to the rest"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "flex-basis",
        "kategorie":  "Flexible Box Layout",
        "frage":  "Specifies the initial length of a flexible item"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "flex-direction",
        "kategorie":  "Flexible Box Layout",
        "frage":  "Specifies the direction of the flexible items"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "flex-flow",
        "kategorie":  "Flexible Box Layout",
        "frage":  "A shorthand property for the flex-direction and the flex-wrap properties"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "flex-grow",
        "kategorie":  "Flexible Box Layout",
        "frage":  "Specifies how much the item will grow relative to the rest"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "flex-shrink",
        "kategorie":  "Flexible Box Layout",
        "frage":  "Specifies how the item will shrink relative to the rest"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "flex-wrap",
        "kategorie":  "Flexible Box Layout",
        "frage":  "Specifies whether the flexible items should wrap or not"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "justify-content",
        "kategorie":  "Flexible Box Layout",
        "frage":  "Specifies the alignment between the items inside a flexible container when the items do not use all available space"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "order",
        "kategorie":  "Flexible Box Layout",
        "frage":  "Sets the order of the flexible item, relative to the rest"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "hanging-punctuation",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies whether a punctuation character may be placed outside the line box"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "hyphens",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets how to split words to improve the layout of paragraphs"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "letter-spacing",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Increases or decreases the space between characters in a text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "line-break",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies how/if to break lines"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "line-height",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the line height"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "overflow-wrap",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies whether or not the browser may break lines within words in order to prevent overflow (when a string is too long to fit its containing box)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "tab-size",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the length of the tab-character"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-align",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the horizontal alignment of text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-align-last",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Describes how the last line of a block or a line right before a forced line break is aligned when text-align is \"justify\""
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-combine-upright",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the combination of multiple characters into the space of a single character"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-indent",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the indentation of the first line in a text-block"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-justify",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the justification method used when text-align is \"justify\""
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-transform",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Controls the capitalization of text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "white-space",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies how white-space inside an element is handled"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "word-break",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies line breaking rules for non-CJK scripts"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "word-spacing",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Increases or decreases the space between words in a text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "word-wrap",
        "kategorie":  "Text Properties",
        "frage":  "Allows long, unbreakable words to be broken and wrap to the next line"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-decoration",
        "kategorie":  "Text Decoration Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the decoration added to text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-decoration-color",
        "kategorie":  "Text Decoration Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the color of the text-decoration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-decoration-line",
        "kategorie":  "Text Decoration Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the type of line in a text-decoration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-decoration-style",
        "kategorie":  "Text Decoration Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the style of the line in a text decoration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-shadow",
        "kategorie":  "Text Decoration Properties",
        "frage":  "Adds shadow to text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-underline-position",
        "kategorie":  "Text Decoration Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the position of the underline which is set using the text-decoration property"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "@font-face",
        "kategorie":  "Font Properties",
        "frage":  "A rule that allows websites to download and use fonts other than the \"web-safe\" fonts"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "font",
        "kategorie":  "Font Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets all the font properties in one declaration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "font-family",
        "kategorie":  "Font Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the font family for text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "font-kerning",
        "kategorie":  "Font Properties",
        "frage":  "Controls the usage of the kerning information (how letters are spaced)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "font-size",
        "kategorie":  "Font Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the font size of text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "font-size-adjust",
        "kategorie":  "Font Properties",
        "frage":  "Preserves the readability of text when font fallback occurs"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "font-stretch",
        "kategorie":  "Font Properties",
        "frage":  "Selects a normal, condensed, or expanded face from a font family"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "font-style",
        "kategorie":  "Font Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the font style for text"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "font-synthesis",
        "kategorie":  "Font Properties",
        "frage":  "Controls which missing typefaces (bold or italic) may be synthesized by the browser"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "font-weight",
        "kategorie":  "Font Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the weight of a font"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "direction",
        "kategorie":  "Writing Modes Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the text direction/writing direction"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-orientation",
        "kategorie":  "Writing Modes Properties",
        "frage":  "Defines the orientation of the text in a line"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-combine-upright",
        "kategorie":  "Writing Modes Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the combination of multiple characters into the space of a single character"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-collapse",
        "kategorie":  "Table Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies whether or not table borders should be collapsed"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "border-spacing",
        "kategorie":  "Table Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the distance between the borders of adjacent cells"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "caption-side",
        "kategorie":  "Table Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the placement of a table caption"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "empty-cells",
        "kategorie":  "Table Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies whether or not to display borders and background on empty cells in a table"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "table-layout",
        "kategorie":  "Table Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the layout algorithm to be used for a table"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "counter-increment",
        "kategorie":  "Lists and Counters Properties",
        "frage":  "Increments one or more counters"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "counter-reset",
        "kategorie":  "Lists and Counters Properties",
        "frage":  "Creates or resets one or more counters"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "list-style",
        "kategorie":  "Lists and Counters Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets all the properties for a list in one declaration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "list-style-image",
        "kategorie":  "Lists and Counters Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies an image as the list-item marker"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "list-style-position",
        "kategorie":  "Lists and Counters Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies if the list-item markers should appear inside or outside the content flow"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "list-style-type",
        "kategorie":  "Lists and Counters Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the type of list-item marker"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "@keyframes",
        "kategorie":  "Animation Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the animation code"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "animation",
        "kategorie":  "Animation Properties",
        "frage":  "A shorthand property for all the animation properties (except animation-play-state and animation-fill-mode)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "animation-delay",
        "kategorie":  "Animation Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies a delay for the start of an animation"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "animation-direction",
        "kategorie":  "Animation Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies whether or not the animation should play in reverse on alternate cycles"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "animation-duration",
        "kategorie":  "Animation Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies how many seconds or milliseconds an animation takes to complete one cycle"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "animation-fill-mode",
        "kategorie":  "Animation Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies a style for the element when the animation is not playing (when it is finished, or when it has a delay)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "animation-iteration-count",
        "kategorie":  "Animation Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the number of times an animation should be played"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "animation-name",
        "kategorie":  "Animation Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the name of the @keyframes animation"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "animation-play-state",
        "kategorie":  "Animation Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies whether the animation is running or paused"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "animation-timing-function",
        "kategorie":  "Animation Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the speed curve of an animation"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "backface-visibility",
        "kategorie":  "Transform Properties",
        "frage":  "Defines whether or not an element should be visible when not facing the screen"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "perspective",
        "kategorie":  "Transform Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the perspective on how 3D elements are viewed"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "perspective-origin",
        "kategorie":  "Transform Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the bottom position of 3D elements"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "transform",
        "kategorie":  "Transform Properties",
        "frage":  "Applies a 2D or 3D transformation to an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "transform-origin",
        "kategorie":  "Transform Properties",
        "frage":  "Allows you to change the position on transformed elements"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "transform-style",
        "kategorie":  "Transform Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies how nested elements are rendered in 3D space"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "transition",
        "kategorie":  "Transitions Properties",
        "frage":  "A shorthand property for setting the four transition properties"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "transition-property",
        "kategorie":  "Transitions Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the name of the CSS property the transition effect is for"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "transition-duration",
        "kategorie":  "Transitions Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies how many seconds or milliseconds a transition effect takes to complete"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "transition-timing-function",
        "kategorie":  "Transitions Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the speed curve of the transition effect"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "transition-delay",
        "kategorie":  "Transitions Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies when the transition effect will start"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "box-sizing",
        "kategorie":  "Basic User Interface Properties",
        "frage":  "Tells the browser what the sizing properties (width and height) should include"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "content",
        "kategorie":  "Basic User Interface Properties",
        "frage":  "Used with the :before and :after pseudo-elements, to insert generated content"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "cursor",
        "kategorie":  "Basic User Interface Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the type of cursor to be displayed"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "ime-mode",
        "kategorie":  "Basic User Interface Properties",
        "frage":  "Controls the state of the input method editor for text fields"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "outline",
        "kategorie":  "Basic User Interface Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets all the outline properties in one declaration"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "outline-color",
        "kategorie":  "Basic User Interface Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the color of an outline"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "outline-offset",
        "kategorie":  "Basic User Interface Properties",
        "frage":  "Offsets an outline, and draws it beyond the border edge"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "outline-style",
        "kategorie":  "Basic User Interface Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the style of an outline"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "outline-width",
        "kategorie":  "Basic User Interface Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the width of an outline"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "resize",
        "kategorie":  "Basic User Interface Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies whether or not an element is resizable by the user"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "text-overflow",
        "kategorie":  "Basic User Interface Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies what should happen when text overflows the containing element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "break-after",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the page-, column-, or region-break behavior after the generated box"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "break-before",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the page-, column-, or region-break behavior before the generated box"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "break-inside",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the page-, column-, or region-break behavior inside the generated box"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "column-count",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the number of columns an element should be divided into"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "column-fill",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies how to fill columns"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "column-gap",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the gap between the columns"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "column-rule",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "A shorthand property for setting all the column-rule-* properties"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "column-rule-color",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the color of the rule between columns"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "column-rule-style",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the style of the rule between columns"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "column-rule-width",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the width of the rule between columns"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "column-span",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies how many columns an element should span across"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "column-width",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the width of the columns"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "columns",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "A shorthand property for setting column-width and column-count"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "widows",
        "kategorie":  "Multi-column Layout Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the minimum number of lines that must be left at the top of a page when a page break occurs inside an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "orphans",
        "kategorie":  "Paged Media",
        "frage":  "Sets the minimum number of lines that must be left at the bottom of a page when a page break occurs inside an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "page-break-after",
        "kategorie":  "Paged Media",
        "frage":  "Sets the page-breaking behavior after an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "page-break-before",
        "kategorie":  "Paged Media",
        "frage":  "Sets the page-breaking behavior before an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "page-break-inside",
        "kategorie":  "Paged Media",
        "frage":  "Sets the page-breaking behavior inside an element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "marks",
        "kategorie":  "Generated Content for Paged Media",
        "frage":  "Adds crop and/or cross marks to the document"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "quotes",
        "kategorie":  "Generated Content for Paged Media",
        "frage":  "Sets the type of quotation marks for embedded quotations"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "filter",
        "kategorie":  "Filter Effects Properties",
        "frage":  "Defines effects (e.g. blurring or color shifting) on an element before the element is displayed"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "image-orientation",
        "kategorie":  "Image Values and Replaced Content",
        "frage":  "Specifies a rotation in the right or clockwise direction that a user agent applies to an image (This property is likely going to be deprecated and its functionality moved to HTML)"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "image-rendering",
        "kategorie":  "Image Values and Replaced Content",
        "frage":  "Gives a hint to the browser about what aspects of an image are most important to preserve when the image is scaled"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "image-resolution",
        "kategorie":  "Image Values and Replaced Content",
        "frage":  "Specifies the intrinsic resolution of all raster images used in/on the element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "object-fit",
        "kategorie":  "Image Values and Replaced Content",
        "frage":  "Specifies how the contents of a replaced element should be fitted to the box established by its used height and width"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "object-position",
        "kategorie":  "Image Values and Replaced Content",
        "frage":  "Specifies the alignment of the replaced element inside its box"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "mark",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "A shorthand property for setting the mark-before and mark-after properties"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "mark-after",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "Allows named markers to be attached to the audio stream"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "mark-before",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "Allows named markers to be attached to the audio stream"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "phonemes",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies a phonetic pronunciation for the text contained by the corresponding element"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "rest",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "A shorthand property for setting the rest-before and rest-after properties"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "rest-after",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies a rest or prosodic boundary to be observed after speaking an element\u0027s content"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "rest-before",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies a rest or prosodic boundary to be observed before speaking an element\u0027s content"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "voice-balance",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the balance between left and right channels"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "voice-duration",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies how long it should take to render the selected element\u0027s content"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "voice-pitch",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies the average pitch (a frequency) of the speaking voice"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "voice-pitch-range",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "Specifies variation in average pitch"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "voice-rate",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "Controls the speaking rate"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "voice-stress",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "Indicates the strength of emphasis to be applied"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "voice-volume",
        "kategorie":  "Speech Properties",
        "frage":  "Refers to the amplitude of the waveform output by the speech synthesises"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "marquee-direction",
        "kategorie":  "Marquee Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the direction of the moving content"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "marquee-play-count",
        "kategorie":  "Marquee Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets how many times the content move"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "marquee-speed",
        "kategorie":  "Marquee Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets how fast the content scrolls"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "marquee-style",
        "kategorie":  "Marquee Properties",
        "frage":  "Sets the style of the moving content"
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "em",
        "kategorie":  "Units",
        "frage":  "This unit represents the calculated font-size of the element. If used on the font-size property itself, it represents the inherited font-size of the element."
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "ex",
        "kategorie":  "Units",
        "frage":  "This unit represents the x-height of the element\u0027s font. On fonts with the \u0027x\u0027 letter, this is generally the height of lowercase letters in the font."
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "ch",
        "kategorie":  "Units",
        "frage":  "This unit represents the width, or more precisely the advance measure, of the glyph \u00270\u0027 (zero, the Unicode character U+0030) in the element\u0027s font."
    },
    {
        "antwort":  "rem",
        "kategorie":  "Units",
        "frage":  "This unit represents the font-size of the root element (e.g. the font-size of the \u003chtml\u003e element). When used on the font-size on this root element, it represents its initial value."
    }
]});